[{"answer": "Well, look, when people give speeches, not every fact is always absolutely accurate.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "So he was a bit naughty on the facts, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "I thought that was brilliant.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, they certainly have a lot more than Barack Obama did when Barack Obama got elected president of the United States.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "I had never seen Condoleezza give a political speech.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "I mean, wouldn't you want her as secretary of state again?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I mean, she has given a lot of foreign policy addresses.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "IULIANI: I am Luciano Pavarotti, Placido Domingo man.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Are you a Led Zeppelin, AC/DC man or more of an elevator music guy?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "It does matter that they listen to music.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Does it matter for presidential candidates or running mates, what they listen to on their iPods?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Tomorrow Mitt Romney has got to make the speech of his life, hasn't he?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Very well, thank you.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Governor Luis Fortuno, how are you?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "ORBETT: Oh, there was electricity in the room.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "What was the feeling in the room tonight?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I believe so, actually.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "A home run for you, too?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, the point is they've had four years to fix it and they haven't.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "They've got a bit of a point, haven't they?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Number one issue out there is jobs.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "What advice would you give him if you were having a private conversation with him now?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, I think once you've been on that stage and you come back to the stage for a moment, you really show how good you are on the stage.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "I don't buy it, do you?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Are you concerned at all that he may not have the details to back up the bigger broad picture plan?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Let me tell you, as an Hispanic, when we get around the dinner table, we talk about jobs, we talk about education, to the extent that both Governor Romney and Paul Ryan can deliver a message, a clear message on both issues, that will come across very strongly.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "What's your sense?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "I think it helps him very much so.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "We have heard a lot more, Governor, about Mitt Romney as the man, as the father, as the grandfather, as the husband, is that helping him, do you think, as the American public get to see another side to the guy?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "I agree.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "He has got to rock this crowd tomorrow, hasn't he?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "You must feel at home in a room like this, don't you?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, the conventions aren't just about what happens in the convention hall.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "How are you going to respond next week?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "I may for a little bit.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Now are you joining the party in the Grill now?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I think you saw the real guy there last night.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "What is the real guy like?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Did I say that?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "No, he wasn't.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "But he was a bit disingenuous with some facts today, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "I haven't researched that.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "But what about his GM plum that closed under President Bush that he blamed Obama for in?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "That's not bad.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "What else have you got?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "We're talking about big ideas.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "It's pretty awful to blame him for a plum that closed under the Republican administration?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "I think what the issue is that extremists, when Barack Obama has voted four time to say, if you have a failed abortion and the baby is born alive, you are not allowed to save it.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Are you concerned that will be perceived as anti-women?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "I was a prosecutor.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Is it really advisable to have people like Todd Akin raring their ugly heads coming out with all this gunfire about rape?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Well, this election is bigger than a single issue.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Why would you do that when they basically want to get rid of you?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I do, I do.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Do you believe in gay marriage?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "And so, how can you really support the ticket which is so resolutely opposed not just the gay marriage, but to most gay right?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "I mean, don't you know why there is such a disregarded thing?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "I would do that.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Would you do that?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Jobs in the economy first.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Jimmy?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "What was your thought?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Well, this is the point I was going to bring up.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "He was pretty disingenuous with the facts, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I saw him four years ago a couple times and he was really boring.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "In he going to nail it, or is he going to be, as he is often with these speeches, a little bit disappointing?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Well, just on the presentation part.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "Maeve, how is he going to appeal to you women like you?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "-- and the chart, the power point.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "He would?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "I think it's like Maeve said -- he kind of -- there's that old Hillary Clinton, she's got to be likable enough.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "What are you looking for?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Because they don't know him.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Why don't people like him?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "That's not the business I'm in.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Ben?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "I think he will just hit.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 727, "question": "Hit or miss?", "qSentId": 726}, {"answer": "He will probably be a hit.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Ryan?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Easy audience, probably be a hit.", "docId": "120829pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Hit or miss?", "qSentId": 731}]